George List papers, 1894-2008 C424
Indiana University Archives
- Professional, 1942-2004; undated (Box 12)
  - Grants and fellowships, 1952-2004 (Box 13)
    - Latin American Studies (Box 13)
      - Grant—Sabbatical, 1970 (Box 13)
      - Grants, 1971 (Box 13)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) (Box 13)
      - 1981 (Box 13)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 13)
    - National Endowment for the Arts and Humanities, 1974 (Box 13)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) (Box 13)
      - Research Grant Application, 1966 (Box 13)
      - Research Grant, 1973 (Box 13)
      - Grants, 1973-1980 (Box 13)
      - Senior Fellowship, 1974 (Box 13)
      - Request to evaluate Refranes Dictionary, 1977 (Box 13)
      - Research Grant, 1981 (Box 13)
      - General, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
      - Senior Grant Info (Colombian Album), 1989 (Box 13)
      - General, 1989-1993 (Box 13)
      - Publication Grants, 1990 (Box 13)
      - Fellowships, 1992 (Box 13)
    - National Science Council, 1963-1964 (Box 13)
    - Pan American Union Grant, 1969 (Box 13)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 13)
      - Recording, 1961 (Box 13)
      - General, 1961 (Box 13)
    - Social Science Research Council (SSRC) (Box 13)
      - 1961-1973 (Box 13)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 13)
      - 1991 (Box 13)
    - Telephone Funding Request, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Venezuela, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Wenner-Gren for Herskovits Collection, 1966 (Box 13)
- Compositions, 1926-2008; undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Andante" for flute, oboe, clarinet, French horn, and bassoon, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Andante for Woodwind Quintette" with Revisions, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Animal Pictures" (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Full score, 1936 (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Instrument Parts, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - Around Our House, Twenty-Four Song Pieces for the Young Pianist, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Ballad Opera: A Tale of Peace," lyrics, undated (Box 14)
  - "Ballet Egyptien," arranged by Alexandre Luigini, conductor score, undated (Box 14)
  - "Come Bring With a Noise" from poem by Robert Herrick, Unaccompanied Mixed Chorus, 1948 (Box 14)
  - "Come Bring With a Noise," 1948, "Play Party", undated (Box 14)
  - Compositions (Box 17 Oversize)
    - "'Song' Without Words" for pianoforte, 1926-1927 (Box 17 Oversize)
    - "Scherzino", 1926-1927 (Box 17 Oversize)
    - "Idylle" for flute, clarinet, and piano, 1926-1927 (Box 17 Oversize)
    - "Semitic Chant" for flute, clarinet in Bb, viola, and cello, 1926-1927 (Box 17 Oversize)
    - "Lament" for flute and pianoforte, 1926-1927 (Box 17 Oversize)
    - "Suite Orientale" full band, 1926-27 (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Country Dance", undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - Crazy Over Horses (A Horse Opera in Three Improvised Scenes), undated (Box 14)
  - "The Dancing Lamb" for piano, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Delta Upsilon Toast (Loyalty Song)", undated (Box 14)
  - Education Division, Rhythm Band Book Volume 1, Text and Piano Score, undated (Box 14)
  - Gadgets (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Act I, 2001 (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Act II, 2001 (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Act III, 2001 (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Gavot" and "Minuet", undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Gavotte" and "Jig", undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Gavotte," "Sarabande," and "Gigue" scores, 1935 (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Go Tell Aunt Rhody," arr. by G. List, undated (Box 14)
  - Gregory Fox Piano Solos, 1960 (Box 14)
  - Hand Graphs, undated (Box 14)
  - "Hushabye", undated (Box 14)
  - "I Wonder as I Wander", undated (Box 14)
  - "Jugoslav Polka" for Band, 1950 (Box 14)
  - "Jugoslav Polka" instrument parts, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - Marche O'Malley (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Violin I, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Violin II, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Viola, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Cello, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Bass, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Piccolo, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Flute I, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Flute II, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Oboe I, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Oboe II, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Bb Clarinet I, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Bb Clarinet II, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Bassoon I, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Bassoon II, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Bb Trumpet I, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Bb Trumpet II, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - French Horn I, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - French Horn II, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Trombone I, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Trombone II, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Trombone III, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Tuba, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Snare Drum, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Orchestra, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Menuet" and "March", undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "O My Darling Troubles Heaven with Her Loveliness", undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Prelude for Organ," "Come Bring With the Noise", undated (Box 14)
  - "Play Party" copies (full, condensed), undated, Music for Children, 1952 (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Prelude", undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - "Prelude for Organ", undated (Box 14)
  - Published Sheet Music, 1947; 1953 (Box 14)
  - Publishing Correspondence for Compositions, 2008 (Box 14)
  - "Scherzino", 1944 (Box 14)
  - "Sontatina" for piano in 2 movements, undated (Box 14)
  - "String Quartet" Parts, Violin II, Viola, Cello, Violin I, undated (Box 14)
  - "String Quartet" Score, undated (Box 14)
  - Unfinished Sonata, undated (Box 14)
  - We Build a Town score, undated (Box 17 Oversize)
  - What Helps Business Helps You: A Musical Morality play by George Lisitsky, undated (Box 14)
  - Works Progress Administration Federal Music Project of New York City Music, undated (Box 14)
- Audiovisual, 1941-1985; undated (Box 15)
  - Cassette Tape Albums (Box 15)
    - Letters, No. 1-12, 12 cassette tapes, undated (Box 15)
      Online Streaming in Media Collections Online
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/pv63gg68d
    - Letters, No. 13-24, 12 cassette tapes, undated (Box 15)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/7w62fr87k
    - Letters No. 25-36, 12 cassette tapes, undated (Box 15)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/fx71b360z
    - Letters No. 37-48, 12 cassette tapes, undated (Box 15)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/dv140990t
    - Letters, No. 49-60, 12 cassette tapes, undated (Box 15)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/mc87q668p
    - Letters, No. 61-72, 12 cassette tapes, undated (Box 15)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/4x51j1335
    - Letters, No. 73-84, 12 cassette tapes, undated (Box 15)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/d217r6603
    - Letters, No. 85-96, 12 cassette tapes, undated (Box 15)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/gm80jb89s
    - Letters, 12 cassette tapes, undated (Box 15)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/sb397r632
    - Index Letters, March 15, 1977, February 4, 1985, 8 cassettes, undated (Box 15)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/v979vk64t
  - Cassette Tapes (Box 16)
    - Krm. #1, Tape 14, Side 2, Chpt. 12, page 535-551, undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/vt151183f
    - My Book Tape 5 Revision, undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/1n79hm645
    - IVFO-R Tape #6, undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/td96kk11c
    - Index to tapes of TR for IFM book, Contents of tapes containing songs used in Folk Song book, undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/h989rm30f
    - Delia's response to instructions from 5/27/04, Tape 9, side 2, Chpt. 8, page 313- 334, undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/6m312623s
  - Compact Discs (Box 17 Oversize)
    - Compositions by George List, undated (Box 16)
    - George List I, undated (Box 16)
    - George List Music, undated (Box 16)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 16)
  - Filmstrip, 1965 (Box 16)
    https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/n583zb977
  - Open Reel Tape (Box 16)
    - List-389, Copies of cuentos from Colombia, Cinta 1 (1st pt), undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/bn999p76v
    - List-390, Copies of cuentos from Colombia, Cinta 1 (2nd pt., concl.), undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/gf06gm11v
    - List-391, Copies of cuentos from Colombia, Cinta 2 (1st pt.), undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/8p58pw071
    - List-392, Copies of cuentos from Colombia, Cinta 2 (2nd pt., concl.), undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/jh3449000
    - List-393, Copies of cuentos from Colombia, Cinta 3 (1st pt.), undated (Box 16)
      ttps://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/wd376d375
    - List-394, Copies of cuentos from Colombia, Cinta 1 (2nd pt., concl.), undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/cc08hz87g
    - List-395, Copies of cuentos from Colombia, Cinta 4 (1st pt.), undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/z316qj37p
    - List-396, Copies of cuentos from Colombia, Cinta 4 (2nd pt., concl.), undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/34850087r
    - List-397, Copies of cuentos from Colombia, Cinta 5 (1st pt.), undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/rx914623x
    - List-398, Copies of cuentos from Colombia, Cinta 5 (2nd pt., concl.), undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/xw42nr88c
    - List-399, Copies of cuentos from Colombia, Cinta 6 (1st pt.), undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/9p290t83v
    - List-400, Copies of cuentos from Colombia, Cinta 6 (2nd pt., concl.), undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/nk322w83w
    - List-401, Copies of cuentos from Colombia, Cinta 7 (one tape only), undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/zw12zp623
    - WTIU Broadcast concerning student activities – boycott, meetings, etc., May 11, 1969, with additional comments by G. List, undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/5h73qd07c
  - VHS (Box 16)
    - Musical Bow/Conjunto de Cumbio, undated (Box 16)
      https://media.dlib.indiana.edu/media_objects/fb494s37w
  - Vinyl Record (Box 17 Oversize)
    - "Andante for Woodwind Quintette" by George List, Parts I & II, 1941 (Box 17 Oversize)